So let's actually go through a real example of how someone might describe doing laundry.
因此，让我们通过一个真实的例子来描述某人如何描述洗衣服。
One very very common household chore I'm sure we've all done laundry at some point.
一件非常常见的家务活，我敢肯定我们都曾在某个时候洗过衣服。
We have to be clear.
我们必须清楚。
But again we're going to try to make it a little bit more interesting and not totally boring.
但是我们再次尝试让它更有趣一点，而不是完全无聊。
OK.
好的。
My clothes are always strewn around my room remember strewn means strewn means all over on the floor
我的衣服总是散落在我的房间里记得散落意味着散落意味着到处都是
on the chair.
在椅子上。
OK.
好的。
So when I need to do laundry I have to get them all in a pile and then sort them into two smaller piles
因此，当我需要洗衣服时，我必须将它们全部堆成一堆，然后将它们分成两个较小的堆
colours and whites colors and whites.
颜色和白色 颜色和白色。
These are the two piles that I make.
这是我做的两堆。
OK.
好的。
I'm a bit picky like that.
我就是这样有点挑剔。
What does that mean.
这意味着什么。
Picky.
挑剔。
I don't like to just get everything all together and throw it in.
我不喜欢把所有东西都放在一起然后扔进去。
I'm a little bit picky and that means I like to have this this way and this this way I like to have
我有点挑剔，这意味着我喜欢这样，我喜欢这样
this thing in this pile.
这东西在这堆里。
The whites over here the colors over here maybe even blue there and yellow there maybe.
这里的白色，这里的颜色可能甚至是那里的蓝色和那里的黄色。
Probably not.
可能不是。
But this is a way to make it a little more interesting.
但这是一种让它变得更有趣的方法。
I'm adding something about myself I'm a bit picky like that.
我正在添加一些关于我自己的东西我有点像那样挑剔。
I have to separate laundry baskets and I always wash colors separately.
我必须分开洗衣篮，而且我总是分开洗颜色。
OK so not everybody has two laundry baskets.
好吧，不是每个人都有两个洗衣篮。
This person has two laundry baskets which kind of shows how picky he or she is.
这个人有两个洗衣篮，这表明他或她有多挑剔。
OK let's go on.
好的，让我们继续。
My family's washing machine is in the bathroom and it has a dial with settings for different temperatures
我家的洗衣机在浴室里，它有一个刻度盘，可以设置不同的温度
times and load sizes.
时间和负载大小。
OK.
好的。
So if there's another machine it's probably the dryer.
因此，如果有另一台机器，它可能是烘干机。
That's the one that's usually the same size.
那是通常大小相同的那个。
They often come in a set in America.
他们经常在美国成套出现。
They come in a set usually and after you take things out of the washer or washing machine you put them
它们通常成套出现，在您从洗衣机或洗衣机中取出东西后，您将它们放入
in the dryer.
在烘干机中。
It's not as common to hang clothes up although some people do.
尽管有些人这样做，但将衣服挂起来并不常见。
OK my family's washing machine is in the bathroom and it has a dial with settings for different temperatures.
好的，我家的洗衣机在浴室里，它有一个刻度盘，可以设置不同的温度。
OK.
好的。
Dial is a circle.
表盘是一个圆圈。
And there's another circle in the middle that maybe it's called a knob a knob and then it has different
中间还有一个圆圈，可能叫做旋钮一个旋钮，然后它有不同的
things around the outside.
外面的东西。
And you can turn this knob and get the right settings the settings the settings are the things you change
你可以转动这个旋钮并获得正确的设置设置是你改变的东西
usually for something that has electronics in it an electronic device for example your cell phone you
通常用于其中包含电子设备的电子设备，例如您的手机
have a settings menu and you can change different things on your phone or about your phone in settings
有一个设置菜单，您可以在手机上或在设置中更改手机的不同内容
so a dial with settings for different temperatures times and load sizes.
所以一个带有不同温度时间和负载大小设置的表盘。
Temperatures would probably be cold water warm water and hot water.
温度可能是冷水温水和热水。
By the way sometimes people use Luke which mine is my name lukewarm anyway.
顺便说一句，有时人们使用卢克，无论如何我的名字是不冷不热的。
Then we have then we have temperatures times which would be maybe 30 minutes.
然后我们有温度时间，可能是 30 分钟。
So I guess you could say one group of clothes is called a load.
所以我想你可以说一组衣服被称为负载。
We use the word load one load of laundry a load of laundry and load sizes would probably be no small
我们使用“装载一担洗衣物”这个词，一担洗衣物，装载量可能不小
and maybe medium large and what that probably means but it usually means is how much water is going
也许是中大，这可能意味着什么，但通常意味着有多少水
to be added to it if you only have a few things and you put that in there.
如果你只有一些东西并且你把它放在那里，就可以添加到其中。
It's a small load size.
这是一个小负载大小。
Maybe the machine only needs to use a little water if you have a huge load of laundry put that in it
如果您有大量衣物放入机器中，也许机器只需要使用一点水
needs to add more water.
需要添加更多的水。
So you would choose something like that.
所以你会选择这样的东西。
A large load or sometimes a heavy heavy load sometimes it depends on the machine.
大负载或有时重负载有时取决于机器。
Temperatures times in load sizes.
负载大小的温度乘以时间。
I do the colors first and then do whites in the second load in the second load.
我先做颜色，然后在第二次加载的第二次加载中做白色。
OK so first colors and then whites.
好的，所以首先是颜色，然后是白色。
These are the two groups of clothes although we don't usually use groups here.
这是两组衣服，虽然我们这里通常不使用组。
I actually hand wash a lot of my linens or anything delicate.
我实际上手洗了很多床单或任何精致的东西。
OK so linens are usually very light clothes.
好的，所以亚麻布通常是很轻的衣服。
That means they're not very heavy.
这意味着它们不是很重。
And if you put them in with other other clothes they might be broken or damaged or anything delicate.
如果你把它们和其他衣服放在一起，它们可能会被打破或损坏或任何脆弱的东西。
So for example underwear maybe underwear would be considered delicate and we can sometimes call those
因此，例如内衣，也许内衣会被认为是精致的，我们有时可以称之为
delicate.
精美的。
My mom yells at me if I put delicate in the machine my mom yells at me if I put delegates in the machine.
如果我把精致的东西放进机器，我妈妈会对我大喊大叫，如果我把代表放进机器里，我妈妈就会对我大喊大叫。
So if I put maybe underwear in the machine she yells at me again I'm trying to make the story a little
所以如果我把内衣放进机器里，她又对我大喊大叫，我试图让故事变得更简单
more interesting.
更有意思的。
I'm describing a process but I'm trying to add a little bit of interesting hopefully personal detail.
我正在描述一个过程，但我正在尝试添加一些有趣的个人细节。
OK.
好的。
Last piece of this laundry story I add detergent according to the measurement line.
这个洗衣故事的最后一篇我根据测量线添加了洗涤剂。
So if there is a cup that we use to measure remember that detergent is the soap that we use.
因此，如果有一个我们用来测量的杯子，请记住洗涤剂是我们使用的肥皂。
There's a line here maybe for small and in line here for a heavier load.
这里有一条线，可能是小型的，这里有一条线，用于较重的负载。
So maybe I will fill up the cup to the measurement line.
所以也许我会把杯子装满到测量线。
OK.
好的。
I add detergent according to the measurement line on the cap of the bottle.
我根据瓶盖上的测量线添加洗涤剂。
So this little cup actually goes on to the detergent the detergent bottle.
所以这个小杯子实际上是放在洗涤剂瓶中的洗涤剂。
It's used as the measuring cup or measuring cap.
它用作量杯或量帽。
Then set the machine for colors and turn the dial remember the dial to thirty five minutes after the
然后将机器设置为颜色并转动表盘记住表盘到三十五分钟后
final spin cycle finishes.
最后的旋转周期结束。
So the spin cycle is the last thing that happens when you put your laundry in.
因此，旋转周期是您放入衣物后发生的最后一件事。
It fills up with water.
它充满了水。
It gets all soapy.
它变得很肥皂。
There are lots of we can say suds mixing around with your clothes and then it goes back and forth Juju.
有很多我们可以说泡沫与你的衣服混合，然后它来回移动 Juju。
And it goes through many cycles at the very end.
它在最后经历了许多周期。
You want to rinse out your clothes right.
你想把你的衣服洗干净。
You want to get them rinsed so there's no soap in them and you want to try to get them as dry as possible.
你想让它们冲洗干净，这样它们里面就没有肥皂了，你想让它们尽可能干燥。
So usually the machine will spin them very quickly to try to get all that water out and get all maybe
所以通常机器会很快地旋转它们，试图把所有的水都排出来
the soap out.
肥皂出来。
If there's any there this is usually called the spin cycle spin cycle spin cycle.
如果有的话，这通常称为自旋循环自旋循环自旋循环。
After the final spin cycle finishes.
在最后的旋转周期结束后。
I take everything out and air dry my clothes on a clothesline hanger drying rack.
我把所有东西都拿出来，在晾衣绳衣架上晾干衣服。
All of these are ok clothesline hanger drying rack in the summer it takes forever for things to dry.
所有这些都是好的晾衣绳衣架晾衣架在夏天它需要永远晾干。
So again I'm trying to add something interesting not just specific details I'm trying to fit it all
因此，我再次尝试添加一些有趣的东西，而不仅仅是特定的细节，我试图适应这一切
together in to something continuous.
一起成为连续的东西。
Give all of the key words I need to give.
给出我需要给出的所有关键词。
Make sure the process is clear but also add a little bit of interesting detail.
确保过程清晰，但还要添加一些有趣的细节。
There's no need to say in the summer it takes forever to dry.
没有必要说在夏天它需要永远干燥。
But I add it just to make it a little bit more interesting and you can do that when you're describing
但我添加它只是为了让它更有趣一点，你可以在描述时这样做
instructions or any kind of process that you may need to describe.
说明或您可能需要描述的任何类型的过程。